acfx.com 2016-06-22

# Privacy Policy | Online Forex Trading |ACFX

## 1\. Personal Information

Considering our nature of business and to perform our services offered to you efficiently, we will collect personal information.

## 2\. Application

In order to open an account with ACFX, you must first complete and send an application form with the required documents. By completing the application form you are requested to disclose private information in order to enable the Company to evaluate your application and comply with relevant rules and regulations.

This information is also used by the Company to inform you regarding its services.

## 3\. Confidentiality and Client's Personal Data Protection

ACFX is registered with the Office of the Commissioner for Personal Data Protection of the Republic of Cyprus; therefore, any clients’ personal data is kept by ACFX according to the Processing of Personal Data (Protection of the Individual) Law of 2001, its amendment (Law No. 37(I)/2003) and the Regulation of Electronic Communications.

ACFX shall not disclose to a third party, any of its clients’ confidential information unless required to do so by a regulatory authority of a competent jurisdiction; such disclosure shall occur on a ‘need-to-know’ basis, unless otherwise instructed by a regulatory authority. Under such circumstances, the Company shall expressly inform the third party regarding the confidential nature of the information.

Clients accept and consent that ACFX may, from time to time, contractually engage companies for statistical purposes in order to improve the Company’s marketing; as a result, some or all of the clients’ personal data may be disclosed on an anonymous and aggregated basis only.

## 4\. The personal information that will be collected from you includes:

  * personal details you provide to us on applications and other forms,
  * financial details such as estimated annual income and net worth and your trading experience and investment knowledge,
  * documents that you provide to us to verify your identity, such as your passport, utility bills, and/or bank statement or your company incorporation details.

According to our regulatory regime we need to keep your personal information on record for a period of at least five (5) years, which is calculated after the execution of the transactions or the termination of the business relationship or in the case you wish to terminate your working relationship with us. 

  * to confirm your identity;
  * to assess your suitability to the products and services we provide;
  * to process your transactions;
  * to provide you with transaction and post transaction related services;
  * to inform you of products and/or services that may be of interest to you;
  * to keep you updated on the issues that are relevant to your business relationship with us;
  * to improve the Site;
  * to analyse statistical data to enable us to provide you with better products and/or services.

## 5\. Legal Disclaimer

ACFX will disclose your personal information, without notice when required to do so by law or in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) protect our rights and/or comply with any court order or judicial proceedings; (b) avoid any potential fraud; (c) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on ACFX or the site; (d) protect and defend the rights or property of ACFX and its family of Websites, and, (e) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of ACFX, its Websites, or the public.

## 6\. Cookies

ACFX uses cookies to gather information about your access to our website and other services we provide to you. Cookies are small pieces of information which use a unique identification tag and are stored on your device as a result of you using this website or other services we provide to you.

Most internet browsers are set up to accept cookies. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may be able to change the settings of your browser to refuse all cookies or to have your computer notify you each time a cookie is sent to it, and thereby give yourself the choice whether to accept it or not. However, this may impair the quality of the services that we provide to you in relation to your account.

## **How ACFX uses cookies:**

ACFX websites use cookies to provide the functionality you need to browse our site correctly. ACFX websites issue cookies upon landing on our websites, unless the user has changed cookie settings in their browser to refuse cookies.

ACFX does not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information about you – the cookies that we use only collect anonymous information to optimise our services and do not collect personal information.

Please note that not all the cookies on our sites are set by us. Please see the section below on third party cookies.

**ACFX website cookie types**  
---  
Session cookies (ACFX) | Analytical cookies (ACFX)  
Functional cookies (ACFX) | Third party cookies  
  
**Session cookies** save website ’session’ credentials for visitors both logged in and not logged in. Once the browser is closed, the cookie is deactivated – and the session closed.

**Analytical cookies** collect visitor information, such as the number of visits, how our website was found, from where the visit came from, if via a marketing campaign etc. This information is extremely important to the business and helps us improve our website and further enhance visitor experience.

**Functional cookies** are specifically about visitor experience on the website. For example they ‘remember’ the open/closed status of pop up messages, enabling access to information stored when registered with ACFX and so on. Without these functional cookies, no settings information can be saved.

**Third Party cookies** are set by other websites who place cookies on the user’s computer. The "3rd party" cookies are placed when you are logged into their service and ACFX does not control the dissemination of these cookies. These cookies are session, analytical and functional, and determine if the user is logged into a social network already, and control bookmarking or sharing ACFX content. Other third parties should be contacted directly to view their cookie privacy information.

## 7.Consent

By visiting and/or accessing this website, you consent to ACFX to collect, maintain and use your personal information as per this policy.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

Your e-mail address may be used by the ACFX in relation to its products and services (including any marketing campaigns related to these products or services). If you do not wish to receive such marketing material please send an email stating so to [support@acfx.com](mailto:support@acfx.com)
